## **Curriculum vitae**



# Mohammad Amir Jamali

mohammadamirjamali2020@gmail.com

Mashhad, Iran 🔾

21 September, 1991 iii

GitHub 🕥

LinkedIn in

I have a Master's degree in Information Technology Management- E-Commerce, as well as, a proven track record in several programming languages. Additionally, I have extensive experience in launching and managing new startups. Along with programming, I am particularly fond of studying Machine Learning (Auto Trading Systems, Life-cycle Assessments) and Quantum Computing(QML).

### **EXPERTISE**

- Machine Learning (Neural Networks and other Machine Learning techniques)
- Microsoft Certified IT Professional (MCITP 2008)
- Programming Languages:
  - > **JS**: JavaScript, Node, React, AJAX, NextJs, Express, Redux, Socket.io (MERN Stack)
  - PHP: WordPress Theme and Plugins Customization (Woocommerce, Stripe Connect, WC Vendor, Redis, Elastic Search, Creating Gutenberg Blocks, Elementor, WP CLI...),
  - > Python: Web scraping (Scrapy, Selenium), Django (DRF, Redis, Celery, PyTest, Locust, Silk, Postgrsql), Cirq(Quantum Computing), TensorFlow
  - ➤ **MQL** (c++): Expert Advisor programing

#### RESEARCHES

- An introduction to Quantum Computing; Advantages and challenges (6th National Conference on Distributed Computing and Big Data Processing) 2021
- Comparison of the local generalization error model (LG Trader) with the exponential moving average (EMA) in selecting stocks with the highest return rate 2019 (Fourth National Conference on Applied Research in Electrical Engineering, Mechanics, Computer and Information Technology.)
- Predicting Bitcoin price with Bayesian Neural Network by using COT weekly report(Master's thesis) 2019

#### SELECTED HONORS AND AWARDS

- Involved in finalists of UCL Hatchery Social Enterprise Award with Enviroble.Ltd (Santander Awards 2022)
- Ranked as the second-highest GPA among MSc students in the Computer Science faculty, with a GPA of 3.88/4.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**



Enviroble.com

**University College London BaseKX** 

03/2021 - 11/2022

London-UK

Founder 🛡

cikit.ir

01/2020 - 02/2021

Mashhad-Iran

Founder Class724.ir

**Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan** 

05/2017 - 11/2019

Birjand-Iran

**Partner** 

Daneshjooyar.com

**Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan** 

10/2015 - 01/2017

Birjand-Iran

### **FAMILIAR WITH**

AWS DevOps

Github Actions

System Design

Git / GitLab

Microservice Architecture

Jenkins

Agile Methodologies

RabbitMQ

Travis-CI

Docker kı

kubernetes

Postgrsql

MongoDB

Cassandra

Terraform

#### **EDUCATION**

Master's in Information TechnologyE-Commerce

Islamic Azad University, Birjand branch 09/2017 - 11/2019

**Bachelor's in Industrial Engineering** 

Payam Noor University, Birjand branch 11/2009 - 02/2014

# **SKILLS**

Teamwork

Innovation

Research

Creativity

Flexibility

# **INTERESTS**

Music

Workout

Travel

Technology

**Environmental Activities** 

Workout

## **LANGUAGES**

English Professional Arabic Native Farsi Native